Which health insurance plan offers you the
best protection? ADFC Argo
Optima Secure, ICICI Lord Elevate,
or Tata AIG Medical Premium? Let's see
which plan
best suits your healthcare needs. Let's start
with ADFC Argo Optima Secure. Its minimum entry age is 18
years for adults and 91 days for children. The maximum
entry age is 65 years for adults and
25 years for children. Now, coming to the sum insured, the
minimum sum insured is ₹5 lakh and the maximum sum insured is ₹2 crore. There is no
limit on the sum insured. Pre-hospitalization is covered for up
to 60 days and post-hospitalization
is covered for up to 180 days. Day care and all treatments are
covered. Its USP is that the plan
doubles your cover amount from day one. Non-
medical expenses are also covered up to the sum insured. You
get a no-claim bonus of ₹50 lakh every year, with a
maximum of
100%. Now, let's talk about ICICI Lord
Elevate.  Minimum entry age: 6 years
Individual 91 days Floater plan for
children: 91 days to 5 years Maximum
entry age: There is no upper age
limit for adults. Age limit for children is up to 30 years.
Now let's talk about the room rent limit.
Single private room without limit on
choosing add-ons. Pre-hospitalization is
covered up to 99 days and post-
hospitalization is covered up to 180 days
All treatments in day care are covered 100%
super no claim bonus is available every year, which can
cover up to unlimited sums.
Initial and PD waiting periods are 30 and
36 months, which can be reduced with add-ons.
Now let's talk about Tata AIG
Medicare premium. Minimum entry age:
18 years for adults and
91 days for children.  The maximum entry age is
65 years for adults and 25 years for children.
Sum in short is
minimum Rs 5 lakh and maximum Rs 3 crore. There is no room
limit on this.
Now coming to pre-hospitalization,
which is covered up to 60 days and post-
hospitalization is covered up to 90 days. Daycare
treatments of up to 41 days are covered.
Its USP is that this plan
offers a unique restoration benefit. The sum insured is stored
once for unrelated illnesses after
just 45 days.
Modern treatments are also covered and non-
medical expenses are also covered for up to seven months. There is a
no-claim bonus every year at 50, the
maximum of which is 100%. The initial
and PD waiting periods are 30 and 24 months.
Choosing the right health insurance plan according to your healthcare needs is very
important. ADAC RG Optimus Secure
Immediate Cover  Doubling offers
ICICI Loard Elevate Global treatment
flexibility and Tata AIG Medical
Premier provides extensive day care coverage and
restoration benefits. Evaluate
these features against your healthcare priorities
and make the best decision for your family.
So that's all for this
video. If you found this video helpful, then do
subscribe to Sun Shots
[Music]